{
    "subject": "resource/Marcus_Rose",
    "predicate": "ontology/school",
    "object": "resource/Loughborough_Grammar_School",
    "human_readable": "Marcus Rose attended Loughborough Grammar School.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854201674461365,
            "question": "When did Marcus Rose attend Loughborough Grammar School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9491907358169556,
            "question": "Was Marcus Rose a student at any other schools besides Loughborough Grammar School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9161284565925598,
            "question": "Where did Marcus Rose attend school?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8540431261062622,
            "question": "What is the name of the school Marcus Rose attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8003418445587158,
            "question": "What other notable people attended Loughborough Grammar School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7202293872833252,
            "question": "What type of institution was Loughborough Grammar School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5419079065322876,
            "question": "Is Loughborough Grammar School located in England?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3864215314388275,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Marcus Rose?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3080919682979584,
            "question": "What year was Marcus Rose born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1936669647693634,
            "question": "Does Marcus Rose have any siblings?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marcus Rose attended Loughborough Grammar School.",
            "html": "dbpedia_432_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Marcus Rose born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_432_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Marcus Rose?",
            "html": "dbpedia_432_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Loughborough Grammar School located in England?",
            "html": "dbpedia_432_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_432_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe text mentions the following sentences related to Marcus Rose's education and life:\n\n* \"Rose was educated at Loughborough Grammar School...\"\n* \"...He played for Leicester Tigers at the age of 17...\"\n* \"...He represented the Barbarians and is the only Englishmen to have been selected to play for The French Barbarians.\"\n\nThese statements clearly indicate that Marcus Rose attended Loughborough Grammar School, making the statement \"Marcus Rose attended Loughborough Grammar School\" true according to the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information in the documents explicitly mentions that Marcus Rose was educated at Loughborough Grammar School."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}